needsupply.com 2019-04-26

# Privacy Policy / Need Supply Co.

Hello. Welcome to [NSTO](https://www.nsto.com/) Web sites, which include but are not limited to [NeedSupply.com](https://needsupply.com/) and [Totokaelo.com](https://totokaelo.com/) (the "Sites"). [NSTO](https://www.nsto.com/) respects your privacy and we are committed to maintaining and using this information responsibly. This privacy policy addresses the use and disclosure of personal information we collect from you. By visiting our website, or providing your information to us, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this privacy policy. 

### Use and Collection of Information

[NSTO](https://www.nsto.com/) collects customer information in an effort to improve our customers’ shopping experience, to communicate with our customers about our products, services and promotions, and to enhance and improve the performance and accuracy of our operations and the Sites. We collect information such as your name, e-mail and postal address and credit card numbers that you provide to us when you place an order, when you save your information with us or when you participate in a sweepstakes or promotion. [NSTO](https://www.nsto.com/) may use your information collected online to process and fulfill your order. We also collect e-mail addresses at various locations within the site including when you order from the site so that we can send you any necessary e-mail messages related to your order. We may also contact you with marketing and promotional materials and other information, from any of our retail brands, that may be of interest to you. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications or contact us at [help@needsupply.com](mailto:help@needsupply.com). In addition, we maintain a record of your product interests, purchases and whatever else might enable us to enhance and personalize your shopping experience.

To serve you better and improve our performance, we may combine information you give us online and in our store. We may also share your information with our affiliates and with third party service providers that provide support services to us or that help us market our products and services. We may also disclose your information when you ask us to do so or when we believe it is required by law. In the unlikely event of a sale of some or all of our business, [NSTO](https://www.nsto.com/) may disclose your personal information to a purchaser that agrees to abide by the terms and conditions of this privacy policy.

You can always review, update and remove your personal information by logging into the website and accessing your account. Please call our customer service line at [+1 (804) 256-2987](tel:+18042562987) or email [help@needsupply.com](mailto:help@needsupply.com) if you need assistance with reviewing, updating or removing your personal information. When you update your personal information, we may keep a copy of the prior version for our records. 

[NSTO](https://www.nsto.com/) may store some information on your computer in the form of a "cookie" or similar file. These files allow us to tailor our websites to reflect your listed or historical preferences. Most web browsers allow web users to exercise control over such files on their computers by erasing them, blocking them, or notifying the user when such a file is stored. Please refer to your browser's instructions to learn about those functions. Please note that if you disable or delete these files you may not have access to certain features and services that make your online experience more efficient and enjoyable. These and other technologies also allow delivery of advertising that directly relates to offers that may be of interest to you. If, however, you'd prefer not to receive relevant banner advertisements, you may opt out at any time by visiting [www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

[NSTO](https://www.nsto.com/) also uses other methods of automatic collection to determine information about visitors to our websites, including your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type or the webpage you were visiting before you came to our Sites, pages of our Sites that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our Sites, access times and dates, and other statistics. We use the information obtained using these tools to provide better customer service, enhance our product offerings, and detect potential misuse or fraud.

### Security

[NSTO](https://www.nsto.com/) works to protect the security of your information during order transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts order information you transmit. While we implement these and other security measures on our sites, please note that 100% security is not always possible. You play a role in protecting your information as well. Because your password permits access to your personal information, please keep your passwords secret and do not disclose it to others. 

### Children

The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act imposes certain requirements on web sites directed at children under 13 that collect information about those children, and on web sites that knowingly collect information about children under 13. [NSTO](https://www.nsto.com/) Sites are not directed at children under 13, and [NSTO](https://www.nsto.com/) does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under 13.

### Links to Other Websites

The Sites may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave the Sites, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy policy. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy policy applicable to the website in question.

### Your Rights

You have certain rights in connection with the data we collect about you. Specifically, you have the right to:

  * Erase your personal data;
  * Rectify or correct your personal data;
  * Restrict the processing of your personal data; and
  * Receive your personal information.

Should you have any questions about these rights, please contact [customerexperience@nsto.com](mailto:customerexperience@nsto.com).

### How You Can Access or Change Your Personal Information

You have the right to request your data; you can review and edit your personal information at any time by logging into your account and reviewing your account settings and profile. You can also close your account through the Sites. If you close your [NeedSupply.com](https://needsupply.com/) or [Totokaelo.com](https://totokaelo.com/) account, we will mark your account in our database as “Closed”, but may retain personal information indefinitely collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, prevent fraud, enforce our Terms and Conditions, or take other actions as required or permitted by law. However, if you close your account, your personal information will not be used by us for any further purposes, nor sold or shared with third parties, except as necessary to prevent fraud and assist law enforcement, as required by law, or in accordance with this privacy policy.

### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

From time to time, we may review and revise our privacy policy. We reserve the right to change our privacy policy at any time and to notify you by publishing an updated version of the policy on [NSTO](https://www.nsto.com/) retail websites.

Last updated: 02/25/2019
